[
    {
        "level": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following is a European country that starts with 'M'?",
        "answers": ["Morocco", "Monaco", "Mitzerland", "Madrid"],
        "correct_answer": "Monaco"
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct freezing point of water?",
        "answers": ["-100 C", "0 F", "0 K", "32 F"],
        "correct_answer": "32 F"
    },
    {
        "level": 3,
        "question": "Who was the first US President to be impeached?",
        "answers": ["Andrew Johnson", "James Monroe", "Warren Harding", "Bill Clinton"],
        "correct_answer": "Andrew Johnson"
    },
    {
        "level": 4,
        "question": "Finish the phrase: The early bird gets the ___?",
        "answers": ["disease", "worm", "present", "burn"],
        "correct_answer": "worm"
    },
    {
        "level": 5,
        "question": "Which of these classical composers wrote 24 caprices for solo violin?",
        "answers": ["Beethoven", "Bach", "Paganini", "Mozart"],
        "correct_answer": "Paganini"
    },
    {
        "level": 6,
        "question": "How old did America become in the year 2023?",
        "answers": ["247", "300", "512", "219"],
        "correct_answer": "247"
    },
    {
        "level": 7,
        "question": "Which country has the greatest population in 2023?",
        "answers": ["Nigeria", "Germany", "Bangladesh", "Indonesia"],
        "correct_answer": "Indonesia"
    },
    {
        "level": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following words unscrambled is a condiment?",
        "answers": ["ynsamisaeo", "bcqsaue", "koetchp", "oeahtudnsymr"],
        "correct_answer": "oeahtudnsymr"
    },
    {
        "level": 9,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a capital city?",
        "answers": ["Toronto", "New Delhi", "Moscow", "Washington DC"],
        "correct_answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "level": 10,
        "question": "How many super bowls did Tom Brady win?",
        "answers": ["12", "10", "6", "7"],
        "correct_answer": "7"
    }
]
